https://www.wheaten.org/privacy-policy/

Wheaten.org
Home
About Wheatens
Did you know?
Privacy Notice
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for Wheaten.org and the Soft Coated Wheaten Terrier Club of Southern California (SCWTCSC). This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:
1.What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
2.What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
3.The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
4.How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via email at Webmaster(at)Wheaten.org
Share this:TwitterFacebook
Wheaten.org > Privacy Policywheaten.orgYour cart is emptyVisit The ShopMember Login Member Login
Pages of InterestWheaten Wares
“Vision of Love” Specialty Dinner
NEW! Videos of Recent Shows
Performance Sports
Training & Other Fun Activities
Grooming
SCWTCSC in the News
AKC & SCWTCA Publications
Select Month
December 2020  (1)
October 2020  (2)
September 2020  (1)
January 2020  (3)
December 2019  (1)
October 2019  (1)
September 2019  (1)
August 2019  (1)
July 2019  (1)
April 2019  (1)
December 2018  (1)
October 2018  (1)
May 2018  (1)
April 2018  (1)
December 2017  (1)
November 2017  (1)
October 2017  (2)
September 2017  (1)
June 2017  (1)
May 2017  (1)
November 2016  (1)
October 2016  (2)
July 2016  (1)
May 2016  (1)
April 2016  (1)
March 2016  (4)
February 2016  (8)
January 2016  (2)
November 2015  (1)
October 2015  (2)
August 2015  (1)
July 2015  (1)
June 2015  (1)
April 2015  (1)
November 2014  (1)
October 2014  (1)
November 2013  (2)
October 2013  (1)
April 2013  (1)
March 2013  (1)
February 2013  (1)
June 2012  (1)
May 2012  (1)
April 2012  (2)
March 2012  (1)
November 2011  (2)
August 2011  (1)
July 2011  (8)
May 2011  (1)
Major dog show superintendents for our region:
InfoDog
Jack Bradshaw
Jack Onofrio
Medical Information Disclaimer: Always consult your family veterinarian in matters concerning the health of your pets. Do not rely solely on information contained within the web pages of "Health" of the SCWTCSC web site, or e-mails generated in-conjunction with the website usage, in lieu of consultation with a qualified veterinarian. It is not the intention of SCWTCSC to provide specific medical advice, but rather to provide users with information to better understand their Soft Coated Wheaten Terrier's health and their diagnosed disorders. The materials available on the "Health" portions of the SCWTCSC Website (and any web site we provide links to) are intended for informational purposes only. The SCWTCSC does not provide veterinary medical services via the Internet.
There is nothin' better than a Wheaten greetn'
Copyright Wheaten.org. All Rights Reserved.
